

CONTACTS

Republic of Belarus, Brest tel. +375 (29) 723 00 90 email: victor.chizh@mail.ru telegram: t.me/ViktorChizh

github.com/ViktorChizh

linkedin.com/in/ViktorChizh

codewars.com/users/ViktorChizh

offerheap.com/specialist/ViktorChizh

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR Vocational training Typescript, React, Redux, Redux-Toolkit, RTKquery, Redux-Saga, Jest, Storybook, Postman, Styled Components, RadixUI, etc. 2023

Educational center "Leader" HTML, CSS, JavaScript 2022

Belarusian National Technical UniversityEngineer GPA: cum laude

ONLINE COURSES

<u>Front End Development Libraries</u> <u>freeCodeCamp</u>

Responsive Web Design freeCodeCamp

<u>JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures</u> <u>freeCodeCamp</u>

LANGUAGES

Russian - native

English - Pre-Intermediate A2 (in progress)

VIKTOR CHIZH

ABOUT ME

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Hi, I am a Front-end developer with -2 year of development experience in creating SPA.

I work with technologies such as React, TypeScript, Redux, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query and other related libraries.

Constantly improving my skills and I want to expand them with new technologies like Vue.js, React Native and others.

My goal is to eventually become a Full-stack developer.

In my free time, I enjoy solving problems on Codewars and learning about new technologies, also improve my English level.

I am always open to new opportunities and would be happy to chat and consider your proposals. Additional information in <u>Portfolio</u> or in <u>LinkedIn</u>.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Roug Arts

Jun. 2024 - Avg. 2024

Project for creating a gaming application in Telegram as a front-end developer.

Key responsibilities:

- Responsive layout based on Figma designs.
- Code optimization and identifying necessary components.
- Interaction with the backend.

Stack: React, TypeScript, HTML, SCSS, Git.

IT-incubator

Nov. 2023 - May 2024

I consolidated my knowledge and filled in existing gaps. The training process closely simulates real production. In the end, I secured an internship on the Instagram project, working with a team consisting of a PM, 2 QA engineers, 6 front-end developers, and 2 back-end developers.

Projects: Social network, Flash cards, Inctagram

Key Responsibilities:

- Team development using Git.
- Full auth flow. Form processing and validation.
- Create private routes and redirecting.
- Covering applications with tests using Jest.
- Improving performance and optimization.

Stack: React, TypeScript, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query, React Hook Form, Storybook, Jest, Git.

Relotech Solution

Jun. 2023 - Dec. 2023

Commercial internship as a front-end developer on a Relocate project (aggregator of statistical data about countries of the world).

The work was carried out:

- a full-stack team of 15 people (back-end, front-end, UI/UX, QA, DevOps engineer, BA, PM)
- according to the Agile methodology with daily sprints
- using a task-tracker ClickUp

Stack: Next.js, MobX, React, React-router, React DOM, HTML, SCSS, Git

SKILLS ✓ HTML ✓ CSS, SCSS, SASS ✓ JavaScript ✓ TypeScript ✓ React ✓ Next.js ✓ MobX

- Redux, Redux Toolkit, RTK-query, Redux-Saga V Jest V Git
- 🗸 Styled Components 🗸 Bootstrap 🗸 MaterialUI 🗸 RadixUI
- 🗸 Storybook 🗸 Postman 🗸 ect.